<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DevOps blog by Vishwas</title><link>http://vishwas1234567.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on DevOps blog by Vishwas</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 05:00:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://vishwas1234567.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Devops2</title><link>http://vishwas1234567.github.io/blog/posts/devops2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 05:00:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vishwas1234567.github.io/blog/posts/devops2/</guid><description>DevOps is the approaching collectively of each improvement and operations groups right into a coordinated workflow such that collaboration and productiveness are stepped forward to satisfy shared commercial enterprise goals. Building on Agile and Lean, DevOps permits the commercial enterprise to reply to modifications and meet patron wishes faster. Tools and automation are essential enablers. Practices which include Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery are regularly followed.
Traditionally, merchandise had been monolithic in nature and launch cycles had been long.</description></item><item><title>Devops1</title><link>http://vishwas1234567.github.io/blog/posts/devops1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 04:58:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vishwas1234567.github.io/blog/posts/devops1/</guid><description>Even as DevOps adoption maintains to boost up in each big firms and web-local agencies, confusion lingers approximately what precisely the time period means. Is DevOps a lifestyle, a movement, an approach, a philosophy, or a few amalgam of numerous of those matters? Or does DevOps suggest various things to extraordinary humans?
However you outline DevOps, reaching DevOps achievement absolutely calls for a journey. And irrespective of in which you&amp;rsquo;re on your DevOps journey, we assist you to solution some of essential questions, consisting of:</description></item></channel></rss>